(十年前)
你妈妈永远都不会懂
There is nothing a father wouldn't do for his son.
父亲对儿子是毫无保留的
Your mother never understood this.
她把你当成了怪物
She looked at you and saw a monster.
而我看到的是潜力
I saw potential.
强盗要是抢了你的钱 弄瞎他的眼
When a bully took your money, you took his eye.
他们要是敢说你疯了 割了他们的舌头
When they called you crazy, you took their tongues.
今天把你带到这里
But I brought you here today.
是显示我的慷慨吗?
Was it generosity?
还是我的爱吗?
Love?
都不是
No.
是告诉你 我的一切不会随我而逝
It's so what I built doesn't die with me.
属于我的一切都会给你
So my legacy can live on,
这就是父子传承的意义
because a father and his son is everything.
我有一个活 只能托付给唯一信任的人
I have a job that I can only trust with one man.
就是你
You.
我手下最精锐的守卫在保护着我们的金库
My most ruthless soldiers were watching our cash houses,
但他们让这个多米尼克·托雷托烧了属于我的东西
and they let this Dominic Toretto burn what is mine.
我要杀了多米尼克·托雷托
I'll kill Dominic Toretto.
把他们都杀了
I'll kill 'em all.
杀了他们？ 你会宽恕他们吗？
Kill them? You'd show them mercy?
不 儿子
No, my son.
当你遭受了痛苦 不要把死亡作为回击
When suffering is owed, never accept death as a payment.
应该让托雷托也尝一下你受到的痛苦
Make Toretto suffer.
(里约热内卢)
(警察局)
现在开始行动
Now the work begins.
那么从今天起
And in there,
今天我们要让我们的家族走上真正的权力之路
today we'll put our family on a path to real power.
开始吧
Let's get started.
发生什么事了
有人要抢金库
-有人要抢金库 -什么
抢金库
靠
Shit!
跟紧他们
在桥上他们跑不过我们
他们人太多
Hey, there's too many of them!
-我们跑不掉了 -我们是跑不掉了
- We're not gonna make it. - You're right. We aren't.
-但你可以 -我不能丢下你
- You are. - No, I'm not leaving you.
要按照计划来
Now, you stick with the plan.
这就是我的计划
It was always the plan.
他们跑不掉了
他要干什么
干掉他
Get him.
《速度与激情10》
(洛杉矶)
你学会了
You had it.
我根本没学会
I didn't have it.
没有人一生下来就会开车
B, no one starts at the finish line.
要对此有信心
You got to have faith.
记住今天的经验
Remember today's lesson.
找准线
Find the line,
感受车
feel the car,
飞速疾驰
and let it fly.
-害怕也没关系
- It's okay to be afraid.
有时候恐惧就是最好的老师
Sometimes fear can be the best teacher.
我没害怕
I wasn't scared.
-谁都有害怕的时候 -你没有
- Everyone gets scared, son. - You don't.
你从来没害怕过
You're not afraid of anything.
我们该走了
We better hurry.
曾祖母坐飞机来了
Great-Grandma just flew in.
她要做拿手菜炸甜蕉
And she's making her famous maduros.
得在罗曼叔叔吃光前赶回去
We got to get to those before Uncle Roman does.
你现在知道害怕了吧
Now, that's something to be afraid of.
你已经死过一回了
You have been dead.
-该焕发活力了 -我早说过了
- It's time to get you living. - Told you guys,
我不需要
I don't need that.
给你  资料填好了
There, profile done.
不用客气
You're welcome.
一般等上个三四天就好
Now, you give it about three, four days...
没人会这么快撩你
It never happens instantly.
什么情况
Wait, what? Hmm.
(配对成功)
让我再看看你的头像
Let me see your profile picture again.
他肯定是开滤镜了
He must have put a filter on there.
你们在看什么
What are you guys looking at?
-停下  不要不要不要看 -我们只是在玩游戏
- Oh, wait. No, no, no, no. - They're just video games, man.
-等会先别看 -只是普通的游戏
- H-H-Hold on, man. - Just videos, man.
我能坐你旁边吗
Can I sit next to you?
你会漂移了吗
You drifting yet?
当然
I am.
你在就好了  我刚才可厉害了
You should've seen us. It was so cool, Mom.
听我说
Hey!
孩子们快过来
!¡Oye, familia!
哎呀我快饿死了
I am starving!
快来
Come on.
我想和你们所有的人好好拥抱一下
I also want a hug from every single person in--
哦  好久不见了
Oh.
-啊  -你看到排的队了吗
- Ah. - You see the line?
都排队等着抱抱呢  祖母
We're all waiting in line for this love, abuelita.
-哦  太好了 -等着你们品尝呢
- Oh, yeah. - Wait till you taste this.
太好吃了
It's really good.
我费了好大的功夫
I put myself out for this one.
好了各位先安静一下
Okay, everybody pipe down, please.
祖母有话想要对大家说
Abuelita would like to say something.
都先安静一下
Piping and downing, please.
每当我看着这优秀的一家人
As I look out at this wonderful family,
我都会感觉到特别骄傲
I am filled with so much pride.
-要是我的儿子 -你们的父亲
The kind of pride that my son-- your father--
还活着他也肯定会骄傲
would have enjoyed if he were here.
我知道你们这一路走来很不容易
I know that this road has been very hard
还遇到了很多不公
and also not fair.
但你们还是走到了今天
And yet here you are,
克服了重重困难
despite all of the odds,
做出了非常伟大的
building this magnificent
成......
leg...
做出的成就将会一代一代流传
It is a legacy that will go on for generations.
谁也夺不走
No one can take it away.
无论是现在
Not now.
还是未来
Not ever.
对啊
Yeah!
为家人干杯
To familia.
干杯 干杯
Familia.
永远是一家人干杯干杯
Siempre. Always.
哎我今天穿了新鞋哦  别玩了
Hey, these new Nikes, man. Stop playing! Goddamn...
别这样罗恩 特工局让你指挥
Come on, Roman. The agency put you in charge,
不是你说让我开车吗
and you said I get to drive.
其实我真正需要的
See, what I really need
是你的头脑
is I need your brain.
罗曼皮尔斯头一回说这种话
Words Roman Pearce has never said.
嗯再跟我说一遍 说详细一点
So talk me through it again. I need details.
好吧  特工局收到了有关被窃军事硬件的消息
Yeah, the agency got a tip on some stolen military hardware.
一辆载有下一代计算机芯片的车
Tomorrow, a next-gen quantum computer chip
明天会出现在罗马
will be transported through the streets of Rome,
我们负责偷芯片
and they need us to steal it.
我查过罗曼的情报了
I checked Roman's intel.
没问题
It's legit.
当然没问题
Of course it's legit.
毕竟那是罗马
We're talking 'bout Rome.
罗马 罗曼
Rome. Roman.
这次的任务
Come on, man.
简单的就像抢劫自家后院一样
That's like planning a heist in my backyard.
你唯一知道的不过是罗马两个字怎么写
Only thing you know about Rome is "ro-man" noodles.
有件事你还没有跟我们解释清楚
One thing you didn't explain to us is:
为什么需要无线电遥控车
Why the hell do we need a RC car,
黄金兰博基尼还有12罐笑气-好了
a gold Lamborghini and 12 tanks of laughing gas?
我参加 你确实需要
Yes, I'm in, 'cause you are definitely
有脑子的人来帮你
going to need all the brains you can get.
净出馊主意
You up to something.
-哎 罗曼 -别跟我说话
-Hey, Rome... - Don't talk to me, man.
别跟我说话
Don't talk to me.
-好吧 -都听好了
- All right. - You know what?
你们都给我放尊重点
The disrespect is gon' have to stop.
现在开始
Now!
那只是我的--你们都听明白了吗？
That's just my-- You know what I'm saying?
我只是在练习怎么说话听起来像老大
Me just, you know, practicing my leadership voice.
我懂你什么意思
I see what's going on.
特尔佳  你别以为自己很聪明
Tej, you think you slick, bro.
不是吧
Look at you.
来探我的底
Spying on me.
你怎么装了个古董
What's up with this old boat anchor?
不带燃油喷射
No fuel injection.
我以为按你的水平
I mean, I'd expect something bigger
会装的规格更高的呢
and better from you, Dom.
我和小布在一起组装这辆车
Little B and I are building it together.
化油器这玩意能让他乖乖听我话
The carburetor forces him to listen.
这就是现在年轻人的问题
That's the problem nowadays.
-没人愿意听话了 -那你得小心了
- Nobody listens anymore. - Well, you better watch out.
等他长到12岁
Little man's gonna be a better wrench than any of us
他的改装水平肯定超过我们所有人
by the time he's 12.
所以我才要培养他
I mean, that's the whole point, isn't it?
传承下去
Pass it down.
下一代会比我们更强
Each generation better than the last.
没错
That's true.
这才是父亲
That's fatherhood.
当初在多米尼家偷油罐车的小贼
Come a long way from the two of us popping gas trucks
-竟然走到了现在 -谁能想到啊
- in the D.R., huh? - We sure did.
那时候可真不容易啊
Those were some tough times.
那时候也很幸福
Those were some great times.
你们你们俩在开会吗
Oh, you... Y-Y'all was in a meeting?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我 我没想打扰你们
I-I ain't want to interrupt y'all.
韩 我们该走了
Han, let's go, man.
罗曼想要指挥这次任务
Roman asked if he could lead this mission.
我怎么能拒绝
How could I tell him no?
但得有你陪他们去我才放心
But you know I can't let them go to Rome without you.
当一辈子洛城飞贼
Los bandoleros for life.
Lo bandolero for life.
你给他争光了
You honor his name.
把我们牢牢记在心里
Hold us in your heart...
你就永远不会迷路
...and you will never lose your way.
你会比我厉害的多
You will be better than me.
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
你
You.
-孩子睡了 -然后呢
- Kid's asleep. - Mm-hmm.
你怎么能越来越漂亮
How do you get more beautiful?
有宝宝了吗
Is it here yet?
没有
No.
要宝宝需要时机
It'll come when the time is right.
今天我和小布练车的时候
You know, when we were in the car today...
小家伙说,爸爸
...B said, "Daddy,
你什么都不怕
you're never afraid."
但其实
But I am.
我会害怕失去儿子
I'm afraid of losing a son.
失去妻子
Or a wife.
那种事不会再发生了
That's not gonna happen again.
只要你想  你可以一直紧紧盯着后视镜看
You can keep your eyes on that rearview all you want.
但这样会错过
But you know what you miss?
什么
What?
眼前的美好
Eternity
既是永恒
in this moment.
我和你现在一样惊讶
I'm as surprised as you are.
我想过上千次怎么杀死你
I've imagined killing you a thousand times.
上一次我们隔着15厘米的钢化玻璃
Last time, there was six inches of reinforced glass,
- 持枪的 - 不
- guns... -  No!
保镖围着你
...guards.
我当时没法杀了你
I couldn't reach you then.
但现在可以
Now I can.
你不如先听听我的遗言啊
You're gonna want to hear my last words.
-多姆 -不要
- Dom! -  No!
那你在杀了埃琳娜之前
Did you hear Elena's last words
听过她的遗言吗
before you killed her?
那你不觉得我是真的有很重要的事情才来找你吗
Then don't you think I'd have a goddamn good reason to be here?
可能是对你来说唯一重要的东西
Maybe the only reason that's ever mattered to you.
小布
Little B.
快醒醒 宝贝
Wake up, sweetie.
有人来找麻烦了
We have an unwanted guest.
按之前说的做
You know what to do.
你到底想干什么
What is it that you want?
说话
Speak.
我今晚遇见了魔鬼
I met the devil tonight.
我一直以为我才是魔鬼
Honestly, I always thought it was me.
我也感觉挺失落的
So that was kind of disappointing.
他直接找到了我
He came to my door.
就这么闯了进去
He let himself in.
据说人在快死的时候
They say when you're facing death,
眼前会闪过人生的走马灯
your life flashes before your eyes.
是这样吗
Are they right?
先告诉我你是谁
I'd start with who you are.
很多人到死也不知道自己是谁
A question most can't answer in a lifetime.
给你3秒钟回答
You have three seconds.
趁你还没在沙发上把血流干
Before you bleed out on my couch,
告诉我你为什么来这
you might want to explain why you're here.
我来这
I'm here
就是因为我敌人
because the enemy
的敌人
of my enemy
就是你
is you.
我这人
I am a man with
无名也无姓
no name.
没什么身份
Heir to nothing.
我来是为了我们共同的敌人
And I'm here for the same reasons you are.
多米尼克·托雷多
Dominic Toretto.
你想杀多姆
You want to kill Dom?
想杀他的人多了
Line's around the block.
不 不
No, no, no.
折磨远比杀死对方要更加残忍
Never accept death when suffering is owed.
我需要你的帮助
But I need your help.
你的工具和技术
Your toys and your tech.
所有的手下
All your boys.
如果不当我的盟友就只能当敌人
'Cause you're either with me or you're...
我和别人一向合不来
I don't play well with others.
那你只能看着你最爱的人死了
Then you'll have to watch who you love most die.
你面前就是我最爱的人
You're looking at who I love most.
你竟然妄想用我的招数来对付我
You thought you could use my own move against me?
我没在和你说话
I wasn't talking to you.
我这是在和奇克
I was talking to Zeke.
埃米尔
Amir.
还有凯文的爸爸
Kevin's dad.
是谁打来的
Who could it be?
真可爱
Cute kids.
他们都有在乎的人
They all had something to take
除了这个可怜虫
except that poor bastard.
连只猫都没有
Not even a kitty cat.
各位可以做出选择
The rest of you have a choice.
选我还是
Me or...
你想要掌控世界
You want to control the world.
而我想惩罚世界
I just want to punish it.
我会记住今天的
I will remember this.
大家都会记住的
I think everyone will.
有人能帮我操作这个东西吗
Huh. I need someone to help me operate this, don't I?
傻子
Nerds?
跟我走好了
Come with me.
要还想见到家人
All right, you know what to do
知道该怎么做吧
if you want to see your families again.
再见
Ciao.
杀了她
Kill her.
该死
Shit.
你们以为我会信任你们吗
Did you think I would trust you?
这年头想找到靠谱的帮手真难啊
It is hard finding good help these days.
大战一触即发
There's a war coming.
是时候选择阵营了
The sides are being chosen.
你爱的每个人都会被毁掉
And everyone you love will be destroyed.
失血2.8升
Lost six pints of blood.
一般1.9升就致命了
Normal person dies at four.
正在把她送往秘密基地
We're shipping her back to our black site.
-有可能挺不过去 -她说的都是真的吗
- She may not make it. - But did her story check out?
市中心确实发生过枪击
We confirmed the shooting downtown,
她的工具都不见了
but her tech wasn't there.
拿走它们的人等于拥有一个电子武器库
And whoever took it now has an electronic arsenal.
-你提醒了你的人了吗 -米亚和布莱恩都很安全
- You've alerted your people? - Yeah, Mia and Brian are safe.
我试过联系诺曼  特尔贾  拉姆齐还有韩
I tried to get in touch with Roman, Tej, Ramsey, Han.
-但联系不上 -他们在哪你知道吗
- No answer. - Any idea where they might be?
在罗马
In Rome.
为你办事
Working for you.
多姆  我们没有  我们没发过罗马的任务
Dom, we don't... we don't have a mission in Rome.
这是个陷阱
It's a setup.
该死
Shit.
我们去罗马
We're going to Rome.
-跟我来 -是的  长官
- Follow me. - Yes, sir.
孩子  我会给你上完这套驾驶课的
Son, you and I will finish that driving lesson.
我向你保证
It's a promise.
无论发生什么
No matter what happens.
我一定会信守承诺的
And I always keep my promises.
上楼去
Head back up.
(罗马)
有没有人能跟我解释一下
So can somebody please help me understand
在我没法开车的情况下
how we're pulling off a mobile heist
怎么才能开车抢劫
but I don't even get to drive?
我们越快闯进卡车里偷走芯片
Well, the sooner we break into the truck and steal the chip,
你就越快能够过上甜蜜生活  懂吗？
the sooner you get to live la dolce vita, okay?
罗曼  护送车队快到指定地点了
Roman, the convoy's almost in position.
你在哪
Where the hell are you at?
你不是负责给我们打掩护吗
You're supposed to be running interference.
罗曼大人闪亮登场
Romey-Rome's in the building.
都给我小心点 可别给我闪瞎了眼
You see me shining, baby.
都好好听我指挥
We on my mission now.
我们当然知道这次是你来指挥
Yeah, we all know that this is your mission.
因为除了你没有人会让韩开那辆古董小轿车
'Cause nobody else on Earth would put Han in an Alfa.
要不是罗曼非要开个带轮子的金库
You know, we'd already be there if Roman wasn't
我们现在早就到了
driving Fort Knox on wheels.
知道引擎盖底下是什么吗
You know what's under this hood, baby.
这辆车超级炫
This car is sick.
这辆老古董虽然马力不行
What this old girl lacks in horsepower,
但开起来还挺灵活的
she makes up for in agility.
说的没错
Yeah, it's true.
虽然兰博基尼装有
While the Lamborghini has a V-10
威驰引擎和三阶段双涡轮增压套件
with a Stage 3 UGR twin-turbo kit,
但你开的古董在这种环境中绝对有优势
the Alfa will definitely have an advantage in this environment.
怎么了
What?
哦 对了我现在也懂车了
Oh, that's right. I know stuff now.
嗯 你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
啊 就这么简单
That's all it took?
特工局的设备
All those agency toys,
也无法联系上罗曼吗
and you still can't reach Roman?
电话电子邮件短信
No cell phone, emails or text messages.
全都没办法联系上韩
Nothing's going through.
我甚至在他的约会软件上勾搭他了
I even tried swiping right on Han's dating app.
下达虚假任务的人准备的很周全
Whoever sent him on this bogus mission
让我们没法提醒他们
made for damn sure we couldn't warn them.
接着跑他们就在附近
Keep searching. They're close.
好了 朋友们露一手吧
All right, everybody, showtime.
开始行动
Here we go!
已就位
In position.
让特尔佳小弟登场
Cue Tiny Tej.
等会等会特尔佳小弟
Wait, wait, wait. Hold up. Tiny Tej?
特尔佳小弟是什么鬼
What are you talking about, Roman? -
都瞧好了 火力全开
All right, all right, fire 'em up!
我可没同意要这么出场
We never agreed on that.
你不是说你想要开车吗 现在就你开
You said you wanted to drive. Now you driving.
你笑什么 别笑了
What are you laughing at? Don't... -
你从哪弄的
Where'd you even get that?
顺便说一句  特尔佳小弟的脑子
Just so you know, Tiny Tej's brain?
可比你灵光
Still bigger than yours.
后方已成盲区
Back is blind.
女士们小心了 这不关“尼姑”的事（谐音梗扣钱）
Watch out, ladies. This ain't "nun" ya business!
小心闪瞎眼
It's time to shine!
进来了我在开车
We're in. I have the wheel.
我们被锁里面了
We're locked inside!
方向盘正在被远程操控
The truck's being steered remotely.
一  二
And a one, and a two, and a...
吓我一跳  怎么回事
Holy shit! What happened?!
炸药放多了  对吧  看好了
Put a little too much in, huh? Ready?
场面火爆啊
That was awesome!
抱歉
Scusi!
那辆卡车被控制了
They're stealing our truck.
还把我们关在了里面
And with us inside.
刚收到报告布罗马广场发生了两起爆炸
Just got reports of two explosions near the Forum.
是他们
That's them.
准备好了？开始......
Ready? And...
等等  听见了吗
Wait, you hear that?
-那是什么声音 -我也不知道
- What the hell is that?! - I have no idea!
该死
Oh, shit.
车里有个巨型炸弹
That's a big-ass bomb!
-什么？-炸弹！
- What? - Bomb!
你不是说这辆车运送的是超级电脑
Roman, you said this was carrying chips
芯片吗
for a supercomputer.
那不是芯片是炸弹
That is not a chip. It's a bomb!
万一它爆炸了怎么办
What happens if it goes off?
什么叫它万一爆炸了怎么办
What do you mean, "What happens if it goes off?"
七丘城都会被炸成两半
The Seven Hills of Rome will be down to two and a half!
城市会化作废墟  无数人丧命
City-wide devastation, countless lives lost.
你知道炸弹是干什么用的吗
You know, the thing bombs do.
我们去找你们
We're coming to you.
好了 呆子们 接下来炸什么
All right, dorks. What are we blowing up?
什么
What?
炸梵蒂冈
The Vatican?
好吧那就炸它
Okay. I'll do it.
你们就等着下地狱
But you guys are going to hell.
是那辆卡车
That's their truck.
谢天谢地多姆来了
Oh, thank God. Dom, Letty.
哦 看看谁来了
Ooh. Look who's here.
来的正好多米尼克
You're right on time, Dominic.
断开加密无线电
Turn off the encrypted radio.
拉姆齐
Ramsey?
卡车被远程操控了  车上有一个炸弹
We're being remote-controlled. There's a bomb on board.
那是一枚DM79型深海高档量冲刺地雷
It's a DM-79 subnautical high-yield neutron mine.
啊 找到了
Ah! Found it.
可以用特工局的紧急关键装置拆除它
I can disarm it with an agency kill switch.
但需要我直接上手操作
I just need physical hands on the device.
-必须拦下那辆卡车 -抱歉美国队长
- We have to stop that truck. - Sorry, Captain America.
我可不答应
Can't let you do that.
要抓紧了  卡车越来越快了
We got to hurry! The truck is speeding up.
-我们必须拦住它 -我要开到车前面去
- We got to block its path. - I'm gonna get ahead of it.
拉姆齐  特尔佳坐稳
Ramsey, Tej, strap in.
多姆  继续开我被堵住了
Dom, go ahead! I'm pinched!
多米尼克
Dominic.
让一让
Come on!
该死的真快
Damn it, he's fast.
就这？晾衣绳？
Really? The clothesline?
既然运不走
Well, we can't drive it,
那就干脆滚出来吧
guess we're just gonna have to roll it.
情况不妙  马上要撞到斜坡了
Holy shit! The truck's about to go over the hill!
-我们必须得撞上去 -你说什么
- We have to crash into it. - We have to what?!
亲爱的小金库我对不起你
I'm so sorry, my gold baby!
停不下来啊
It's not stopping!
炸弹滚出来了
Dom, the bomb is out.
大家离炸弹远点  我来处理
Everybody, stay clear. I got this.
不  是我们来处理
No. We got this.
莱蒂
Letty!
他们变成恐怖分子了吧
Have we made them all terrorists?
已经把他们的照片传给当局了
Their images have been fed to the authorities.
干得好鲍勃  我要去干掉
All right, Bob! I got to go kill that jerk
那些想拆炸弹的混蛋
that's trying to disarm my bomb.
总有麻烦要处理
It's always something, you know? Oh.
你们家人还在我手里别想乱跑
Remember, I still have your families, so don't go anywhere.
人特么呢？
早安 罗马
Buongiorno, Roma!
行吧
All right.
是谁的声音
Man, who the hell is that?
嘿  是你呀
Hey! There he is!
风云人物  罗曼·皮尔斯大队长
Man of the hour. Roman Pearce, team leader.
我要来找麻烦了
Can't wait to see you get out of this one.
哦  莱蒂
Oh, Letty!
我发现幕后黑手了
I think I found our guy.
嘿  莱蒂  去你妈的
Hey, Letty. Vaffanculo!
我来对付他
I'm on him.
加油泵要爆炸了
That pump's gonna blow.
小无名氏  准备起飞吧
Little Nobody, you're up.
- 我现在就 - 喵
- Moving to dis... - Peekaboo!
-赶快下车要爆炸了 -该死
-Get out of there! It's gonna blow! -Oh, shit.
-艺术就是爆炸！
- Boom.
我们得让他的引爆器失灵
We need to jam the detonator now.
知道了知道了,莱蒂你跟紧他
I got it, I got it. Letty, don't lose him.
我们可以锁定你的位置
I can lock on to your location and transmit
然后通过你的手机传送干扰信号
cellular interference through your phone.
应该能让引爆器失灵,争取点时间
That should jam his detonator and buy us some time.
莱蒂
Letty.
真棒
Bravo!
现在有点麻烦
It's getting tricky, guys.
我马上就要跟不上那个人了
I can't stay on him for much longer.
拉姆齐,那条河有多深
Ramsey, how deep is that river?
台伯河吗
The Tiber? Uh...
大约18米深
Uh, 60 feet.
河水能一定程度上缓冲爆炸
I mean, the water could smother the explosion,
大概能弱化炸弹10成的威力
reduce its power by ten times, maybe.
该死
Damn it!
差点就能抓到我了  宝贝儿
You missed me by that much, baby!
我跟丢了  让他跑了
I lost him. He's gone.
可恶
Damn!
他跑出范围了
He's out of our reach.
没法再干扰他的引爆器了
We can't jam the signal anymore.
很遗憾  多姆  我还要继续
Bad news, Dom. I'm back in business.
你还剩30秒来拯救罗马
You got 30 seconds to save Rome.
多姆他一旦引爆炸弹  你也会被炸进河里
Dom, he armed the bomb, and you're almost at the river.
还剩15秒钟  多姆
15 seconds, Dom.
多姆  听我说
Dom, listen to me.
梵蒂冈在炸弹的爆炸范围里
The Vatican's within the blast radius.
快离开
Get out of there.
你已经尽力了
You've done everything you could.
还有办法
Not everything.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
我们都做了什么？
What have we done?
只有让你生不如死  我才能完成我的使命
Through your suffering, I'll fulfill my destiny.
来找我吧
Come find me.
你的痛苦才刚开始
Your pain has just begun.
后会有期  多姆
I'll see you soon, Dom.
据报道
Breaking news from Italy.
意大利首都罗马发生了大规模爆炸
The capital Rome has been hit by a massive explosion.
意大利首都中心发生了一起可怕的爆炸事件
为致命炸弹发生爆炸
为巨型军事物
To be a large military weapon.
此次爆炸波及到了梵蒂冈宫殿
梵蒂冈的部分建筑
The Vatican has sustained
遭到了破坏
some structural damage.
目前没有造成人员死亡
...but no lives were claimed.
此次爆炸规模前所未有
有关部门已查明涉案恐怖分子
Authorities have identified the terrorists as
为以下5人
these five individuals.
这5名恐怖分子是由该男子领队
...as these five individuals, led by this man.
-多米尼克·托雷多 -托雷多 -托雷多
- Dominic Toretto. - Toretto. -Toretto.
-多米尼克·托雷多 -多米尼克·托雷多
- Dominic Toretto. - Dominic Toretto.
执法部门正与多国相关部门合作
Law enforcement is working across borders,
开展有史以来规模最大的
mobilizing an international fugitive hunt
-跨国逮捕行动  -很抱歉长官
- of unprecedented scale. -I'm sorry, sir.
-我不知道她是怎么进来的  -我知道
- I don't know how she got in. - I do.
我偷了你的证件
I stole your badge.
现在用完了  谢谢
I'm done with it now, though. Thanks.
这不是  呃
Well, if it isn't, um--
说实话  我不知道怎么称呼你
Honestly, I-I don't know what to call you.
叫你无名氏小姐吧
Little Miss Nobody?
直接叫我的名字怎么样
How about you call me by my actual name?
之前我听说  泰丝  你正在大马士革执行任务
Last I heard, Tess, you were running ops in Damascus.
你以为就凭你爸是传奇特工
You think you can walk in this room
就能这里想来就来吗
just 'cause your daddy's an agency legend?
我来这里是为了帮被告
I'm here because someone needs to speak
说两句公道话
on behalf of the defense.
在罗马发生的爆炸事件无疑是一场灾难
What just happened in Rome was an unmitigated disaster.
虽然伤亡被降到了最小
Casualties were kept to a minimum,
但却影响了世界
but the impact was global.
你觉得他们去罗马都干了什么
And what do you think happened in Italy?
哦  我猜是看了风景  吃了意大利面
Oh, sightseeing, eating bucatini,
-还偷了一枚2万吨的炸弹 -得了吧  爱慕斯
- stealing a 20-kiloton bomb. - Oh, come on, Aimes.
-你很清楚这是胡扯 -注意措辞
-That's bullshit and you know it. -Careful, now.
现在小无名氏不能参与任务
With Little Nobody out of commission
你爸又不知所踪  我才是这里的新老大
and your daddy in the wind, you're talking to the new boss.
看看吧
Showtime.
洛杉矶  2001年
Los Angeles, 2001.
出身卑微  土生土长
Humble roots, local kids,
从街头赛车手变成抢劫犯
street racers who became hijackers.
接着成为飞车走私犯
Graduated to high-speed smuggling,
驾车越狱抢劫火车
mobile jailbreaks, train robberies.
凡是能开车干的勾当  他们都干过
If it could be done in a car, they did it.
凡是违背常理和地球重力的  他们屡犯不止
If it violates the laws of God and gravity, they did it twice.
这台词是你写的
You write that yourself?
第一次注意到他们是2011年
We first took notice in 2011,
在里约  他们抢劫了一个毒枭  埃尔奈勒耶斯
Rio, when they robbed a drug kingpin, Hernan Reyes,
让他死在了一座桥上
left his body on a bridge.
我的前辈  无名氏先生  看到了他们的潜力
My predecessor, Mr. Nobody, saw potential,
于是把他们纳为了编外人员
so he recruited them-- freelance, of course.
他们帮我们在阿布扎比
They ran missions for us in Abu Dhabi,
东京  伦敦  纽约  蒂比利斯执行过任务
Tokyo, London, New York, Tbilisi.
要我说  好几年前就该和他们撇清关系了
You ask me, we should've cut ties years back,
但总有人支持他们
but they had their champions.
他们用惯用伎俩
That's their M.O.
笼络执法机构
To corrupt law enforcement.
布莱恩·奥康纳
Brian O'Conner.
埃琳娜·内维斯 卢克·霍布斯
Elena Neves. Luke Hobbs.
他们都变成了一家人
Everyone becomes family.
就像一帮爱车的极端分子
It's like a cult with cars.
甚至你爸也成了一份子
Even Tess's dear old dad.
所以我们离堕落
So we're all just
就差这一场烧烤派对吗
a barbecue and a beer away from corruption?
你想说什么
What's your point?
我想说他们是罪犯
Point is they're criminals.
罗马出事并非偶然
Rome was a matter of time.
他们已经偷走了几亿美元
They've stolen hundreds of millions of dollars
还有至少一艘核潜艇
and at least one nuclear sub.
我们怎么能放任他们猖狂这么久
The real question is: How did we let this go on so long?
他们一家帮我们干了不少上不得台面的活
This family has gotten their hands dirty to keep ours clean.
曾经替特工局上过刀山下过火海
They've driven to the gates of hell and back for this agency.
罗马爆炸案有问题很蹊跷
Something is not right with Rome.
不可能是他们做的
It can't be.
一点也不蹊跷
It can and it is.
这不是特工局该有的水平
The agency is better than this.
不该这么容易上当
We are smarter than this.
我们应该支持多姆和他的家人
We should be standing with Dom and his family.
这是我们最应该做到的事
That is the very least that we can do.
如果我们不采取行动  我们所有人都会被波及
If we don't act, this blows back on all of us.
后果会非常严重
The fallout will be existential.
请授予我全面行动权限
I'm asking for full green-light authority.
动用一切手段杀掉或逮捕托雷多一伙
Kill or capture the Toretto clan by any means.
爱慕斯  你在干什么
Aimes, what are you doing?
看来多数人赞成
Looks like the ayes have it.
作为你的直属上司
As your direct superior,
我一点也不在乎对方心地善不善良
I don't give a shit about anybody's heart of gold,
而且我讨厌烧烤
and I hate barbecues.
你知道我强硬起来什么都做的出来
You know I'd make a freight train take a dirt road,
所以劝你别挡我的道
so do not get in my way.
好吧
Okay.
我走我的道
I'll go my own way.
罗马一沦陷  世界都乱了
When Rome falls, so does the world.
不像《罗马假日》那么美好
Well, it ain't no Roman holiday.
你也不是电影男主角
And you're no Gregory Peck.
我的家人呢
My family?
我把他们藏起来  暂时安全
Your team's gone to ground. They're safe for now.
但莱蒂被抓住了
They've taken Letty.
-谁干的 -特工局
- Who's they? - The agency.
你现在是全世界特工组织
And you've just shot to number one
最想抓捕的目标
on the world's most wanted list.
陷害你的人想借此切断你和特工局的联系
Whoever did this wanted to sever your ties to the agency
还想让你和家人分离
and isolate you from your family.
如果你联系家人通话一定会被追踪
Any attempt to contact your team will be traced.
替我给无名氏先生捎一句话
I need you to get a message to Mr. Nobody.
那你得找个灵媒或者魔术师帮忙
You'll need a medium for that or a magician.
他正在玩失踪
He's done his disappearing act.
把话传出去就好
Just get the message out.
告诉他我要去喝比利时啤酒
Tell him I'm ready to have that Belgian,
他就明白了
and he'll know where to go.
我说句心里话孩子
I've got a message for you, ducky.
如今战火四处蔓延  你要是不顾自己
The world is on fire, and you want to keep running
一个劲的往火海里冲去拯救别人
into the burning building to save lives,
你早晚会被大火吞噬
but eventually the building's gonna collapse on you.
我并不怕死
I don't care about dying.
我只是想尽力保护好所有我爱的人
I only care about protecting the people that I love.
知道为什么决斗士总是孤身一人
You know why gladiators never had families?
-为什么 -因为他们知道
- Why? - Because they knew
每天都可能是自己的末日
that every day might be their last.
你选择了一条孤独的路  亲爱的
You're choosing a lonely way, my darling.
没人能陪你走下去
Can't take anyone with you.
用天眼系统
Bring God's Eye online.
遵命  启动中
Yes, sir. Initiating.
找到托雷多一伙的准确位置
Get me Toretto and the others' locations
要精确到毫米
to the millimeter.
长官出问题了
Sir, we have a problem.
天眼跟踪硬件被移除了
The God's Eye tracking hardware has been removed.
是泰丝
Tess.
看来她来这不光是为了找我
I guess her visit wasn't purely a social call.
帮我一个忙
Do me a favor.
一旦发现他的位置就追踪他的行踪
She pops up on any grid, let's see where she goes.
至于其他人我们已经掌握了嫌犯范围
As for the rest, our fugitives aren't unknown quantities.
托雷多有个妹妹  有个儿子
Toretto has a sister, a son.
在找到他之前
Until we find him,
先找他家人
find his family.
哦
Oh!
你又赢了
Again.
你这是跟你最爱的姑姑耍小聪明吗
Are you cheating on-on your favorite auntie?
不管赢了一寸还是一米
It doesn't matter if you win by an inch or a mile.
赢了就是赢了
Winning's winning.
这话听着有点耳熟啊
Where have I heard that one before?
跑快跑
Go! Go!
-全面搜索 -要抓活的
-Search everywhere! -We need them alive!
趴地上别动  趴地上别动
Get on the ground! Get on the ground!
不  米娅放开她
No! Mia! Let her go!
跑
Run!
-你好吗？ -雅各布叔叔？
- What's up? - Uncle Jakob?
你爸叫我来的
Your dad sent me.
稍等一会
Change of plans.
别动
Don't move!
我让你别动
I said don't move!
小布在你那吗
Do you have Little B?
小布
B!
-别动！
- Freeze!
-还好吗 -还好
- You okay? - Yeah.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
小布
B!
快来  快来
Come, come.
那些人是谁派来的
Who the hell were those guys?
特工局  去罗马是个陷阱  我们被算计了
Agency. Rome was a trap. Whole family's being targeted.
我得去找布莱恩和其他人
Okay, I got to get to Brian and the kids...
多姆让我带走他
Dom sent me to take him.
记得世界末日时
Remember that place we said we'd go
要去的地方吗
if the world went to hell?
多姆让我们去那集合
Dom wants the team to meet there.
好
Yeah.
好了  听着
Okay, look.
小布  你跟雅各布叔叔走
Little B, you're gonna go with Uncle Jakob.
好吗？乖乖听他的话  乖
Okay? You do whatever he says. Yeah?
我带你去找爸爸  如果你没意见的话
I'm gonna get you to your dad. If that's okay with you.
你要不惜生命保护他
Protect him with your life.
我爱你  雅各布
I love you, Jakey.
我也爱你  米娅
I love you, too, sis.
出发吧
Let's do it.
天呐不会吧
Oh, my God.
呦
Yo!
不是那辆
It's not that one.
是这辆
It's this one.
好车
Yep.
不会吧
Wait, but...
(那不勒斯)
我想找个人
I'm looking for someone.
各位喝杯酒开心一下
You boys look like you could use a drink.
我来请客怎么样啊
How about a round on me? Huh?
我没骗你们
As a matter of fact,
我能请你们喝光这家店所有的酒
I will buy as many rounds as they can handle.
你要是来这找人就没法活着出去了臭女人
来一杯
Shots? No?
还是来一枪
Shots?
啤酒  要两杯
Beers. Two of 'em.
行
Thanks.
干杯
Cheers.
奎尼告诉我你在这
Queenie told me I could find you here.
比利时啤酒？
Belgian?
无名氏说过他有个女儿
Mr. Nobody said he had a daughter.
是吗
He did?
如今他不知去向
Well, now that he's gone missing,
所以我来接他的班了
I came in from the cold.
你爸爸掌权时没人敢惹事
Your dad kept the agency in line.
现在好像牛鬼蛇神都跑出来了
Now it feels like all the anchors have been cut.
这个世界没有规则  就没有安全可言
In a world where there is no code, no one's safe.
说的对
You're right.
特工局已经违背了它的原则和初衷
The agency has turned its back on everything it stood for.
新任长官埃尔斯正在动用一切资源搜捕你
The new boss, Aimes, he's coming for you with everything.
我在帮你拖延时间
I'm buying you some time.
而且  还借用了他们的追踪小工具
And borrowed their, uh, little tracking device thingy.
眼熟吗
Look familiar?
-天眼 -嗯哼
-God's Eye. - Mm-hmm.
我把它放保险柜里了
I'd put that in a vault somewhere.
保险柜会被从墙里拽出来  还是放我这安全
People pull vaults out of walls, so I think it's safer with me.
我从他们看漏的交通录像里
I pulled a screen grab
截了一张图
off of a traffic cam that they missed,
导入了天眼
put it in God's Eye.
显示人在里约
There was a hit in Rio.
你在那不会刚好有敌人吧
You wouldn't happen to have any enemies in Rio, would you?
-雷耶斯 -埃尔南·雷耶斯
- Reyes. - Hernan Reyes?
已经死透了  但是他有个儿子  但丁
Still pretty dead, but he has a son, Dante.
那你得送我去里约
So you're gonna have to get me to Rio.
这是你的第二个愿望  还剩一个
That's your second wish. You have one more.
莱蒂
Letty.
她被关在秘密监狱里地图上都找不到
Letty's in a black site prison off of every map.
那就救她出来
Then get her out.
没人能做到
Nobody can.
无名氏就能
Nobody would.
多姆  我真的很抱歉
Dom, I'm so sorry,
但是这个愿望根本没办法实现
but what you're asking me to do is impossible.
一切皆有可能
Nothing's impossible.
只要相信你自己
You just have to have faith.
把我藏在装满须后水的集装箱里
Sneaking us out of Rome in a shipping container
运出罗马真是个馊主义  罗曼
full of aftershave, that was a terrible idea, Roman.
等等  我好像闻不到味道了
Wait, I think I lost my sense of smell.
这哪是须后水啊  这是催泪瓦斯
That is not aftershave. That is tear gas.
各位我没觉得有多难闻呢
Hey, man, I don't know what y'all are talking about.
你们懂我吧
You know what I mean?
我现在好香啊
I smell magic.
我要顺手捎走一瓶
I took a bottle for myself.
变成这样都要怪你
This is all thanks to you.
你清楚吧
You know that, right?
别闹了你们只要乖乖听我这个“领队”的话就行了
No, see, you just got to follow my "leat" as a "leater."
懂吗  我天生就是做“领队”的料
You see what I'm saying? I'm a natural-born "leater."
我们在哪
Where are we?
带你回家了  拉姆齐
I brought you back home, Ramsey.
这里的监控摄像头是全世界最多的
The city with the most amount of surveillance cameras.
这可真安全
Perfect.
-我爸知道你开这种车吗 -当然
- Dad know you drive this thing? - He should.
我开着和他赛过车
I raced him in it.
但顺便告诉你在90年代
And just so you know, in the '90s,
能开5.0升引擎的车是很了不起的
if you were rolling in a 5.0, it meant you were the man.
这车可是福特野马
Like it or not, it's still a 'Stang.
所以稍微尊重点
So, you know, respect.
这样吧
You know what?
听点旅行音乐
Traveling music.
我13岁得到的这辆车
I got this car when I was 13.
自己重新上了漆  还改造了发动机
Did the repaint myself. Rebuilt the motor, too.
哎对车的热爱有时是按捺不住的
Ah. Sometimes you just can't help what you love, kid.
我们现在到底要去哪里
Are you gonna tell me where we're going?
是我的一个地盘
A place of mine your dad knows.
去找你爸
We're gonna meet him there.
他还好吗
So he's okay?
我们会在那找到他的
We'll meet him there.
我想要看你汗流如瀑布
他以前是个内衣模特
This guy was an underwear model.
-什么？ -没错
- What? -  Yeah. Oh, yeah.
跟我一起
Here we go and...
小布  身体扭回来  这是一个律动
Little B, bring it back. It's a boomerang.
这是一个律动
It's a boomerang, maybe.
噢 扭的不错
Oh! Look at you!
来享受它
That's feeling it.
这才叫享受节奏
That's called feeling the vibrations.
这歌真过瘾  这活力！这节奏！
It's just energy, man. It's energy. It's vibrations.
享受！享受！
Feel it! Feel it!
(特工局秘密基地)
可以进了  长官
You're clear, Director.
高档外套
Fancy coat.
亮晶晶的耳环
Expensive earrings.
这鞋穿着很疼吧
Those got to hurt.
你是特工局的重要人物吧
You really brought out the big guns, huh?
我不是代表他们来的
I'm not here for the agency.
这可能是你没收的
You could've confiscated that.
你左腕那条伤疤
That scar on your left wrist,
是认识多姆的第一晚留下的
you got it the night you met Dom.
他说当时在炫耀
He said he was showing off.
我在收音器上安了超声波干扰器
I put an ultrasonic jammer on the audio,
但摄像头还是能拍到我们
but the cameras can still see us.
听着  我会带你离开这儿
Look, I'm gonna get you out of here,
但我需要些时间
but it's gonna take some time.
我没时间等了
Time is what I don't have.
我得赶快回到多姆身边
I need to get back to Dom.
我在牢里什么忙也帮不上
I'm no good to anyone in this cage.
我有预感你肯定是做好了准备才来的
I have a feeling you didn't come all this way without a plan.
强者能看透彼此
Game recognizes game.
一旦我开了弓  就没有回头箭了
If I make this move, there's no coming back.
听着合我心意
I like it already.
好吧  首先我带你离开牢房
Okay. First, let's get you out of this cell.
-会有点疼 -嗯？
- It's gonna hurt. - Hmm?
配合一下
Work with me.
打开门！
Open the door!
放倒她！
Knock it down!
守卫  守卫
Guards! Guards!
-救命 -放开她
-  Help! - Let her go!
放开她
Let her go!
你来真的
Really?
真没想到啊
Que surpresa!
你看看
Look at this.
我能走到这儿多亏了你
None of this happens without you.
欢迎回家 很高兴见到你  哥们儿
Welcome home. Good to see you, bro.
迪奥戈  我也很高兴
Diogo, good to see you.
车不错嘛
Ah. Look at you.
对了我听说你被盯上了
So, uh, I hear you got a little heat on you.
没有  我是来找人的
Nah, I'm just looking for someone.
有什么能帮你的
How can we help?
老大他来了
你已经帮上忙了
You already did.
好吧
你们好
是你吗？
别让我哭鼻子  让一让
下一个是谁？
给你介绍个人 他是个人物
I need you to meet somebody. A GOAT.
活着的传奇
A living legend, literally.
我知道他是谁
很难不知道呢
你今晚肯定稳操胜券了
You must be in the winner's circle tonight.
我看你在车上安装了RB26引擎对吧
I see you put in a RB26 in that, right?
2.4升的承受不住这么强的升压
L24 would never handle this much boost.
我的兄弟们也会认可的
My boy back home would approve.
我不在乎别人认不认可
I'm not looking for anyone's approval.
你先别急着否认  看看你的周围
Before you get ahead of yourself, look around you.
大家或多或少都在寻求认可
We're all looking for a little validation.
-你要和我赛车吗
- You racing or what?
我劝你最好别和他起冲突
Trust me, you don't want that smoke.
我今晚来不是为了赢别人的车的
I'm not here for pink slips tonight.
真可惜
我当场就能击败他
这里的人都这么想
You and everyone here.
耶！
Yeah!
谁打败了我就能赢得一百万美元
A million dollars for whoever can beat me.
迪奥戈  拿着
Diogo, here.
真乖
Yes.
伊莎贝尔
Isabel.
恭喜你
谢谢
今晚有场比赛  对吧
There will be a race tonight, yes?
应该有
Yeah, maybe.
-靓女拜托啦  加我一个
- Pretty please, with me on top.
多米尼克·托雷托
Dominic Toretto.
我就知道你会来找我
I knew you would come for me.
很遗憾当时没有在罗马见面
I'm sorry we didn't get to meet in Roma.
我们俩太忙了
We were both so busy.
我是但丁 你好呀
I'm Dante. Enchanté.
你当时真是战神下凡  英勇无畏  帅呆了
And you were fantástico, fabuloso, o cara.
他拯救了梵蒂冈
He saved the Vatican.
还有谁能办到
Who does that?
教皇  还是上帝？
Seriously. The Pope? God?
对了  你看到那场好戏了吗
By the way, did you see what I did there?
其实是在还原
The ball through the city was
我们家保险箱的遭遇
a bit of an homage to my family's safe.
还加了火焰特效
Except it was on fire.
你还记得我爸吗
You remember my father?
-埃尔南·雷耶斯 -是的
- Hernan Reyes. - Yes.
他以为自己能一手遮天  称霸一方
I remember he thought he had his foot on this city's neck.
但你猜怎么着
But you know what happened?
我打败了他
I took him down.
我们别当着大家的面吵架
Let's not argue in front of the children.
你说的一点也没错
You are absolutely right.
我爸爸是个大恶人
My father was a horrible man,
失败的父亲
very bad daddy,
但我还挺喜欢他的
but I kind of liked him.
可你不仅抢了我们的钱  还害了我没了爸
And you took him from me when you stole our money
让我每天活在痛苦里
and left us with nothing but suffering.
我来这就是为了这个
Well, that's what I came here for.
帮你从痛苦里解脱
To end that suffering.
哦  还有  我没抢你们家钱
Oh, and I didn't take that money.
我烧了
I burned it.
啊 噢
Uh-oh.
好吧  巴西由我说了算
Well, Brazil is mine,
这里是我的地盘
and I own this city.
你以为有钱就什么都能买到
You people think you can buy everything.
但你买不来街头人的尊重
But you can't buy the streets.
我们与多姆在一起
We stand with Dom.
这下就尴尬了
Well, this is awkward.
不如我们同时开枪朝对方乱射
So, how about we all just start shooting each other
看谁死谁活
and see what happens?
或者赛车
Or we race.
你赢了就送我坐牢
If you win, you take me in.
你输了
If you lose...
最好别输
Don't lose.
聚到这的人都是为了看赛车
You all came 'cause you wanted to see a race.
那就放马过来
Let's race!
啊  真辣
Ouch.
穿黑衣服开黑车真酷
Black on black look good.
我知道你在好奇什么
I know what you're thinking,
没错  我下面的毛和头发都是一个颜色
and, yes, the carpet matches the drapes.
拉到吧
Thank you.
我竟然要和伟大的多米尼克·托雷多赛车了
I can't believe I'm gonna race the great Dominic Toretto.
人家好激动啊
I have butterflies.
你真是太厉害了
You're just so impressive.
赢了那么多比赛
You've won so many races.
赢得了所有人的爱
Everyone loves you.
还救了那么多条命
You've saved so many lives.
我懂
I know.
你就像
It's like you're a...
大圣人
a saint.
多米尼克大圣人
Saint Dominic.
我一直在研究你
And I've been studying you.
在观察你
And watching you.
但我猜不出来
I can't figure it out.
你会
How...
你会怎么选择
How do you choose?
你会选择去救谁
How do you choose the ones you save?
时间到了
Cheguei.
这里是里约宝贝
各就各位
出发！
耶！
Yeah!
我马上就要赢了
I'm beating you, baby!
你太心急了
You're too eager.
这个感觉才够劲
That's what I'm talking about!
噢  别别 别开那么快了
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. You shouldn't do that.
该我了
多米尼克  你要救谁呢
Dominic, who will you choose?
你要救谁呢  多姆
Who you gonna choose, Dom?
是救那女的
Are you gonna save her?
-还是救你兄弟 -太刺激了
- Or are you gonna save him? - Let's go, baby!
老子赢定了
This race is mine!
点兵点将点到谁
Eeny, meeny, miny...
你在干什么
看来你选好了
Looks like you made your choice.
胜利属于我！喔！
Finally! Whoo!
别走  迪奥戈
Oh, no, Diogo!
刚刚是陷阱题  他们都得死
Trick question. Everyone dies.
And one, two, three.
艺术就是爆炸！
Boom!
耶
Yeah!
我赢了比赛  哈哈
I win, baby!
再来找我  多米尼克
Keep coming, Dom!
以后的好戏还多着呢
There's so much more fun to be had!
坚持住
Come on.
早上好！亲爱的
Good morning, sunshine.
妈的
Goddamn it.
那男的“嘭”一声被炸飞了
And then he was like, "Boom!"
我就“巴拉”一声被震到了 那女的就被惊道“什么鬼”
And I was like, "Blam!" And she was like, "What?"
我就说“闭嘴吧”
I was like, "Shut up."
结果我成了世界第一的赛车手
And now I'm the best racer in the world, so...
别碰指甲  等它晾干
Do not touch that. Let it dry.
你们看着气色不错
You guys look fantastic.
我知道黑色比较显瘦看起来有威慑力
I know the black is very slimming and very scary,
但现在其实流行粉彩色
but the pastels, you know, they're in season,
粉色能弱化一点阳刚之气
and I feel like it tones down the masculinity a little bit,
五大三粗的男人太多了
which we all need these days.
你知道吗
Did you know...
认真听
Listen to me.
你知道吗  在法律意义上我当时死了2分钟
Did you know that I was legally dead for two minutes?
2分钟
Two minutes.
鲍勃  别走神
Bob, pay attention.
猜我看到了什么
And you know what I saw?
空白
Nothing.
完全一片空白
Not a goddamn thing.
但我确实感觉在他
But I do feel like once he, uh...
撞裂我的脑壳后我想开了很多
cracked my skull open, it just opened my mind.
意义深刻对吧
Yeah, that's deep, right?
你说的很对  鲍勃
You're absolutely right, Bob.
该继续干正事了
We should get back to work.
真是个工作狂
Such a stickler.
好了  我想想
All right.  Let's see.
把他们的钱都划走怎么样
Should we take all their money?
你你个小坏蛋
You. You are evil.
谢谢两位当听众
Thank you for listening.
那么  把这里当自己的家吧
So, mi casa, su casa.
晾干指甲油  喝完鸡尾酒
Let these dry, finish those mojitos,
然后很快就会有人来安葬你们的
and, um, someone's gonna come and bury you guys soon.
我要去洗我的秀发了
I'm gonna go wash my hair.
不
No.
什么
What?
好了
All right.
好酷 这是什么
Cool. What is that?
这是一个技术工具包
That's a technical tool kit.
别担心  都是一些
Don't worry, it's just a bunch of awesome stuff
你永远用不着的炫酷工具
that you're never gonna get to use.
好了
Okay.
睁大眼睛  别乱动
Eyes open. Hold still.
别笑这么夸张
Don't smile like that.
怪吓人的
It's unsettling.
搞定  你现在叫切斯特
Sweet. Your new name is Chester...
-切斯特吗 -你在和你帅气的
-Chester? -and you're on a kayaking trip with
有肌肉线条的罗杰叔叔
your handsome,
一起划船旅行
ripped Uncle Roger.
好了
All right.
现在该给你找身新衣服穿了
Now, time to get you some new clothes.
比睡衣稍微时髦点的衣服
You know, something a little more chic than
好吗
pj pants, all right?
-在加油站买吗 -就在加油站买
- From a gas station? - From a gas station.
我真的想不明白
See, I just don't understand.
为什么我们为特工局做了那么多事
Why would the agency turn they backs on us,
他们还要背叛我们
after all we've done for them?
那个疯子把黑锅甩给了我们
That madman pinned it all on us,
把我们变成了头号公敌
and now we're public enemy number one.
多姆会在集合点和我们会合
Well, Dom is gonna meet us at the rendezvous point.
但与此同时我们不能暴露行踪
But in the meantime, we have to stay under the radar.
做好开战的准备
And we got to get ready to fight.
所以我们要搞到枪支  大炮  坦克对吧？
Wait, so we need guns, artillery, tanks?
真棒  但是怎么搞我们现在一分钱都没有
Yeah, but how are we gonna get that with no money?
什么
What?
我们被黑了账户
We've been hacked.
看看每个账户里
Look. Every account.
我们这20几年辛辛苦苦挣的钱全都没了
Every dollar we made over the last 20 years is gone.
全都被划走了
He took everything.
我们东西没抢成还被洗劫一空
We got heisted during our own heist.
-赶快破译......那个 -破译区块链
- Just decrypt the... Yeah. - Decrypt the blockchain.
我正弄呢 这样就能找到交易散列
I'm on it. Then we can find the transaction hash.
交易散列
The transaction hash.
-就能找到收款方的IP地址  -没错
Gets us the receiving IPs. Exactly.
说人话
English.
我们在追踪钱的去向
Following our money, genius.
看看对方把钱转到哪去了
We're trying to see where he sent it.
破解难度很大
The coding is next-level.
我没见过这么复杂的编码
I've never seen anything like this.
需要性能更好的电脑
We need more computing power.
我们已经破产了还怎么买
How are we gonna do that if we broke?
什么叫我们破产了
What do you mean, "we" broke?
难道你藏了私房钱
Wait, you holding out on us?
怪不得你一点都不紧张哥们
No wonder you've been so calm.
兄弟  不然还能是什么情况啊
Bro, what-what d-- what do you think this is, bro?
都听我的  转过身去
You know what? Turn around.
“转过身去”？什么
"Turn around"? What do you...
什么就转过身去
What you mean, "turn around"?
我已经是个成年人了
Man, I'm a grown-ass...
-你要干什么  -罗曼住手
- What...What are you doing? - Hey, Roman, do not.
你现在没穿紧身内裤吧
Please tell me you're not wearing Spanx.
不是紧身内裤  是金身套装
Oh, this ain't Spanx. These banks.
放心吧 哥们  我来帮忙
But it's okay, bro. I got you.
好吧 哈哈
All right?
你懂我吧
You know what I mean?
给 这沓给你
Yeah. That's for you.
这沓给你
That's for you.
我想想啊
Let me see.
韩 你可是个非常靠得住的人
Han, you always good for the bag,
因为你永远都有借有还  对吧
'cause the bag always come back, you know.
借用你们花的每一分钱都要开收据
So what I need from all of y'all, I need receipts.
你以为你是谁  让我给你开收据
Who is you talking to? Got your receipt.
去哪买东西才能不被发现呢
So where do we go to shop off the grid?
我知道一个地方
I know a place.
请各位旅客携带好自己的贵重物品
等等  特工局在追踪我们  我们这样不会暴露吗
Wait. The agency's after us. Aren't they gonna see our faces?
要的就是这样
Yeah, I'm counting on it.
特工守则第一条
The first rule of tradecraft:
先要被找到才能够甩掉
you can't lose a tail if they don't find you.
-不好意思 -不好意思
- Oh, sorry. - Sorry.
我要 这样吧  我要
I'll just-- Wait. You know what, I'm just...
我们要 如果你想先走
We'll just-- If you want to, uh, go.
我们先站在这
Uh, we'll stay here.
-你们绕过去 -绕过去？好的
- You guys, you guys go around. - Go around? Great.
绕过去
Go around.
长官  追踪到了男孩和他叔叔的定位
Sir, we just got a hit on the boy and his uncle.
其他同伙还在欧洲
The rest of the team is still in Europe.
我们正和当地政府取得联系
We're interfacing with local authorities.
别费劲了
Forget authorities.
那伙人从学车开始
These people have been outrunning the cops
就知道怎么甩开警察了
since they could reach the gas pedal.
告诉替我们干过活的小偷  走私犯
Get word to every snitch, smuggler,
杀手和黑客
hitter and hacker we've ever used.
有钱能使鬼推磨
Money talks and so will they.
秘密地A的警报
We're getting an alert
被触发
on Black Site A.
泰丝刚刚探访了莱蒂·奥尔蒂斯
Tess just visited Ortiz.
聊的愉快吗
They have a nice chat?
看来不愉快
Guess not.
给我回放一遍
Run it back for me.
暂停放大
Stop. Zoom in.
回查她的航班信息
Back-trace her flight path.
找出她是从哪来的
Find out where she was before this.
多姆肯定在那
That's where Dom is.
(巴西)
(里约热内卢)
你早就知道我是谁了对吧
You knew who I was all along, didn't you?
我看到你第一眼就知道
From the moment I saw you.
你姐姐笑起来很温柔  为人善良
Your sister smiled with her eyes and led with her heart.
你很像她
Just like you do.
我们俩完全不像
We were nothing alike.
姐姐她心地善良
She was the good sister.
永远有先考虑别人
Always putting others first.
她做的事情永远是正确的
Always doing what was right.
有的时候我就在想  为什么那个死掉的人
Sometimes I would think that the wrong sister died.
是善良的她而不是我
Why the good one and not me?
你一点都不像她是错的
You're wrong about not being anything like her.
你想一想  你姐姐希望听到这种话吗
You think that's what she wants to hear?
从前有一个警察  和一个街道赛车手
A cop and a street racer.
我来讲这个故事吧
I'll tell you something.
从相识开始他们一路追逐
They travel down the same road long enough...
经历了一切才明白彼此很相似
...and they realize how much alike they really are.
相信我
Trust me...
我都懂
...I know.
她并没有止步于此
She's still doing it, isn't she?
她还在帮助别人
She's still helping people.
她在帮助我们
She's helping us.
你知道的  艾琳娜
You know, Elena,
她其实非常了解雷耶斯家族
she knew everything about the Reyes family.
在她的丈夫被杀死后
After they killed her husband,
她耗尽一生只为讨回公道
she dedicated her life trying to take them down.
我这里应该还有她的文件
I think I still have her files.
等等  在伦敦市中心
Wait, so we gonna find military-grade gear
可以找到军用设备吗？
in the middle of London?
你不是说想躲开监控吗
You said you wanted to shop off the grid.
等一下  我们刚刚是穿越了吗
Wait a second. Did we just time-travel?
如果是你  你会在这里
Would you look for a black-market operation
你收到了一份新邮件
in a place like this?
进行黑市交易吗
You've got mail.
-哦  零食 -兄弟  可别忘了开收据啊
- Ooh, snacks. - Get me a receipt, homey.
我要怎么才能让自动售卖机给我开收据
How am I gonna get a receipt from a vending machine?
你就不能想办法让它开吗
How about you figure it out?
交易记录  税收抵免
Paper trail, bruh. For tax write-off.
真是够了
I swear to God...
你好吗  鲍伊420
What's up, Bowie420?
我的天啊  弗雷迪·墨克
Oh, shit. FreddieMerc?
怎么了？认识我之前我也有自己的生活
What? I had a life before you knew me.
经营着一家最为臭名远扬的
Bowie here runs one of the most notorious
网上黑市
online black markets.
你要什么他有什么
If you want it, he'll sell it.
我以为你不喜欢我送你的东西
I thought you didn't like that about me, though.
好吧  非常时期
Well, desperate times.
马芬蛋糕是什么口味
What kind of muffins are these?
哦  那是迷幻马芬蛋糕
Oh, those are fun muffins.
吃下4个以后
You have like four of them,
你就会穿着内裤看《幻想曲》了
you'll be in your underwear watching Fantasia.
你们来就是为了吃马芬蛋糕
Is that what you guys came for? My muffins?
要开马芬蛋糕派对
Oh, it's gonna be a muffin party?
我们需要交通工具
We, uh, we need transport.
武器 车子 各种东西
Weapons, cars, the works.
秘密行动
And quietly.
很好那你付我现金好吧
Cool, then I'm just gonna need cash. Okay?
可别给我加密币之类的
None of that crypto stuff.
黑人版杰夫·贝索斯不会赖账
Oh, the Black Jeff Bezos here got you covered.
-黑人版贝索斯是吧 -他甚至还上过天呢
-Black Bezos? -Yeah, he's even been into outer space.
-哇 -既然要我掏腰包
-Wow. -If y'all was gonna be giving out my money,
我希望花钱之前至少通知我一声
I'd appreciate some type of a heads-up,
懂我意思吧
you know what I'm saying?
说吧要多少
How much we talking about, bruh?
兄弟价钱肯定公道合理
Just like a reasonable amount.
这些够吗
How about that?
这都不够买马芬蛋糕的
That won't even cover the muffins.
这个家伙认真的啊
Is this guy serious?
简直疯了
Shit's crazy. Mm-kay.
拜托  老兄  你可是宇航员哎
Come on, man, you're an astronaut.
那这些呢
Well, how about that?
你把钱都留太空了吗
What, did you leave all your money in space?
老哥都给他吧
Man, give me this.
-谢谢 -你动真格的
- Thank you. - Are you serious right now?
你知道所有钱都得我付对吧
You know I pay for everything around here, right?
本来就该你付这笔钱
You should pay for everything.
都怪你的罗马任务  我们才会沦落到这般境地
It's your mission in Rome that got us here in the first place.
是你的情报引导我们去的罗马
No, it was your intel that led us to Rome.
说真的那个陷阱确实很难识破
To be fair, that setup would have confused the best of us.
不我受够了
No, I'm tired of this.
他只会说大话
'Cause all he do is talk.
大家都得拼命执行任务  也包括你在内
And then everyone has to do their job and yours.
你说什么  特尔佳
What are you saying, Tej?
你知道我在说什么？伙计们
Mean, what I'm saying? Hey, guys.
-这里的氛围很和谐 -搞什么你来真的
- This is a family environment. - What? Really?
-来真的？要打出去打  伙计们
- Really? Take it outside, fellas.
想怎么样  兄弟
So, what we doing, bruh?
两位先生别闹  伙计们
Gentlemen, please! Guys!
-别碰到自动售货机  -不要 -不可思议啊
-Oh, not the vending machine.-No.  -Unbelievable.
伙计们  你们这样我要损失几千美元的
Guys, you're causing like dozens of dollars in damage!
让开吧
Let's go. Come on.
我们要阻止他们吗
Should we stop this?
-停一停 -不  让他们缠在一起吧
-Hold on! - Nah, let 'em bond.
嘿  这电脑可是1998年的
Hey! That computer's from, like, '98!
搞什么  兄弟
What the hell, man?
好吧好吧
Okay. All right.
藏肚兜子里的钱都被你翻出来了
We doing stomachs now.
好了  可以了
All right, all right, that's enough.
-好几年前我就该打醒你 -他打复印机用力过猛
You've been wanting that for years! Uh, I think
结果修好了它
he hit the copy machine so hard it works now.
你这是在干什么
What the hell was that?
就像一名犹太魔术师
He's like a ghetto magician.
你懂我在做什么
You know what it is, bruh.
-我打败了你 -你打败了我？
- I beat your ass. - You just beat my ass?
-打败我？ -天啊
- Beat my ass, huh? - My God,
你俩能别闹了吗
will you two just quit it? Please.
拜托我们没时间胡闹
We don't have time for this. You.
-你快干正事 -我需要做的
- Get to work. - Oh, I just need
就是黑进黑市  很快就能搞定
to hack into the marketplace. It'll just take a second.
不
Oops.
你在干什么  鲍伊  你刚才做了什么
What the hell, Bowie? What did you just do?
哎  抱歉  你们的照片
I'm sorry. Your guys's faces are,
已经传遍了整个暗网
like, all over the dark web.
奖金实在是太诱人了
I mean, that reward is dope.
-啊  啊  -我们必须走了
-  Ow. Hey. - We have to move.
-特工局很快就会到 -听着  我不是针对你们
- The agency's minutes away. - Look, it's nothing personal.
-嘿  迷幻马芬蛋糕我请客 -你想怎样？
- Hey, fun muffins on me, okay? - What? Huh?
啊 啊
Oh! Oh!
我活该
I deserved that.
-你还好吧 -还好  谢谢你  老哥
- Are you okay, bro? - Yeah, thank you, man.
好了  现在该去哪呢
All right, so where to now, huh?
监狱吗
Jail?
我知道一个地方  一个我很不想去的地方
I know somewhere. Last place I want to go.
和我站在一边感觉如何
How does it feel to be on my side of the law?
特工局喜欢先修好东西再破坏掉
They like to fix things before they break 'em.
这地方让人恶心  莱蒂
It's a sick place, Letty.
不用谢
You're welcome.
你做了什么？
What did you do?
我修改了麻醉气体的输送通道  输送到了他们的空调里
I rerouted anesthetic gas into their air conditioning.
再过几分钟那些摄像头就会恢复正常
And I bought us a few minutes before these cameras reset
他们就会发现这里已经变成了睡眠研究所
and they find out this place turned into a sleep study.
你是要继续生闷气  还是想要离开这里呢
You gonna stay grumpy or do you want to get out of here?
他们可不会永远睡着
They're not gonna sleep forever.
你不想回到你宝贵的家人身边吗
Don't you want to get back to your precious family?
该死
Shit.
看起来你都搞定了
Seems like you got this covered.
-你要我帮你做什么 -我有个计划
- What do you need me for? - I have a plan,
但需要2个人才能完成
but it's a two-person job.
很简单吧
Now, was that so hard?
我们有多少时间
How much time do we have?
大概4分钟吧
I'd say about four minutes.
那应该够了
It'll have to do.
我要是你就不会站起来
I'd stay down if I was you.
那你还得再加把劲
You got to hit me harder for that.
你会后悔这么说的
You're gonna regret this.
但丁·雷耶斯
Dante Reyes.
出生于葡萄牙
Born in Portugal.
母亲出生于太平洋诸岛
Mother from the Pacific Islands.
孩提时代他就展现了反社会倾向
Sociopathic tendencies from an early age.
很快他从少管所到了监狱  再到了精神病院
He bounced from juvie to prison to mental wards.
每一次他父亲都会来保释他
And each time, Daddy was there to spring him out.
他父亲去世后他就消失了
After his father died, he disappeared.
雷耶斯生前拥有的一切不动产
Properties Reyes owned before he died.
如今都被出售或者收回了
Now all sold and repo'd.
除了这一个
Except this one.
警察局
The police station.
已经荒废了很多年了
It's been abandoned for years.
你猜产权证上是谁的名字
And guess whose name is on the deed.
但丁·雷耶斯
Dante Reyes.
我会在那找到答案的
I'll find my answer there.
我要跟你一起去
I'm coming with you.
我不希望你再出任何事
I need you to stay safe.
我本可以赢下那场比赛的
I would have won that race, you know.
你想重赛
So you want a rematch?
我要求必须重赛
I'm demanding it.
那好那就稍后见
So I guess I'll see you soon.
瞧瞧
疯子被困在市中心贫民窟了
伙计们  最好别这么做
Guys, you don't want to do this.
他要一块新手表  警官
He needs a new watch, cop.
听着 手表是别人送我的
Look, the watch was a gift.
但我的护裆里有16克拉未切割的钻石
But I got 16 carats of uncut diamonds in my jockstrap
你们想看吗
if you want to take a look.
这下你是需要换换新的表了
Now you really do need a new watch.
真该死
Damn it.
小布 你没事吧
B, you okay?
来口香糖  会好受点
Tried gum? Gum helps.
我一点也不喜欢坐飞机
I don't like planes.
如果是因为恐高  那确实是个问题
If it's the height, that's gonna be an issue.
知道吗  我曾经很怕车
You know, I used to be scared of cars.
我父亲死后  我常常责备自己
After my dad died, I guess I blamed myself.
当时很难受
It was tough.
患过惊恐发作之类的
I had panic attacks, the whole bit.
我当时只敢坐公交
Heck, I took the bus.
对  我当时很担心自己会犯错
Yeah. I think I was just so worried about making mistakes
怕我不会像我哥哥一样优秀
and not being as good as my brother.
-你呢 -拜托
- You? - Uh, excuse me.
你知道你爸爸什么样吗
Have you met your dad?
我时常活在他的阴影下
He casts a pretty big shadow.
啊  好些了吗
Huh. Feeling better?
很好
Good.
我也是
Me, too.
这是您点的饮料  先生
Here's the drink that you ordered, sir.
你认识她
You know her?
是啊 人都得有点高端朋友
Yeah, it's good to have friends in high places.
数到3
On the count of three,
我们站起来去厕所  准备
we're gonna get up and go to the bathroom. Ready?
Three.
那些人是谁呀
Who were those guys?
特工局的  他们发现我们了  我们得甩掉他们
Agency. They found us. Now let's lose our tail.
我勒个去
Holy shi...
打住  只有在歌词里  或者磕到脚趾的时候才可以骂脏话啊
Wait! Swearing is for song lyrics only and stubbed toes.
算了  集中注意力
Forget about it. Pay attention.
这里太高了  我们没法滑翔
Okay? We're-we're too high to glide,
只能俯冲  也就是说
so we need thrust, which means, uh,
呃 燃烧也就是说
combustion, which means...?
氧气和燃料
Oxygen and fuel.
酒精
Alcohol.
那是桃红葡萄酒  没用
That's rosé. Not gonna work.
很难解释  但主动性很不错
Long story. But good initiative.
我很高兴你不恐高
I'm glad it wasn't the height.
享受下降之旅吧  小布
Enjoy the ride, Little B.
鲍伊标记了我们的位置
Bowie tagged us.
特工局正在追赶我们
The agency is on our tail.
我们必须找到装备
We need to find gear
尽快到集合点那里
and get to the rendezvous as soon as possible.
就在这
It's right here.
你们原地待命  这里就交给我吧
You guys hold back. Let me take care of this.
不不 这可不是好主意
No, no, no. Th-That's a bad idea.
-跟罗马任务一样差劲 -什么？
- I mean like Roman-level bad. - What?
你在说什么呀你
What are you talking about, man?
你听到我说的话
You heard what I said.
听着兄弟你用不着这么做
Look, bro, you don't have to do this, man.
我是你的后盾
You know I got your back.
我们都是你的后盾
We got your back.
我必须独自完成
I got to do this alone.
我有些事情想和你谈谈
I have something to talk to you about.
死人会出现在我门前只有一个原因
The only reason a dead guy shows up at my door:
复仇
revenge.
该死
Oh, shi...
-该死 -干 韩！
- Oh, shit. - Shit. Han!
你不该活过来
Should have stayed dead.
我可以  我能进去
I can get in. I can get in.
我不喜欢重复自己的话
I don't like repeating myself.
你糟蹋了我的零食
You ruined my snacks.
冷静  我不想和你打
Relax. I don't want to fight you.
那就速战速决
Then this is gonna end quick.
你带了一堆人来杀我？
You bring more men to kill me?
他们也想杀掉我
They're trying to kill me, too.
看来还有更多的朋友在找我们
Well, it looks like we got more company.
-你还会开车吗 -你说呢
- You still drive? - What do you think?
嗯  再给我点时间
Okay, just give me a second.
别动！
Freeze!
-放下笔记本电脑 -好的
- Drop the laptop! - Okay.
伙计们  我进去了
Guys, I'm in.
别开枪
No, no, no, no!
现在我们扯平了
Now we're even.
你还好吧
You okay?
听着  这些我都能理解
Now, see, I understand all this.
但刚才那是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
-你刚被吓到了  -我看到了
-You got scared. -I saw that.
-我才没被吓到兄弟 -没错他被吓傻了
- Ain't nobody got scared, bruh. - No, you were... he was scared.
有人来找麻烦了
We have an unwanted guest.
我的家人呢
My family?
暂时很安全
They're safe for now.
你从来没害怕过
You're not afraid of anything.
我并不怕死
I don't care about dying.
我只是想尽力保护好所有我爱的人
I only care about protecting the people that I love.
把我们牢牢记在心里
Hold us in your heart
你就永远不会迷路
and you will never lose your way.
你从来没害怕过
You're not afraid of anything.
恐惧就是最好的老师
Fear can be a great teacher.
你从来没害怕过
You're not afraid of anything.
喜欢我那个地方吗
How do you like my place?
可惜我不在那里  没法带你逛逛
I'm bummed I'm not there to show you around.
一想到你看到了我  就有点尴尬
And a little embarrassed you saw my vision board.
哈哈但至少你知道了  为了此时此刻
But at least you know how hard I've been working
我有多努力
to get us to this point.
我只知道你死定了
Now I know you're a dead man.
我可是复活过的人
You mean resurrected.
我要感谢你
Thanks to you.
要不是你开车拽走那个保险箱
You know, if you never would have gotten behind that wheel,
我永远不会变成今天这样
I'd never be the man that I am today.
你的生活是如此的美好
You built such a beautiful life,
佳人相伴充满爱意
filled with love and family.
对我来说遥不可及
I never got that chance.
意外  混乱  死亡
Collateral damage, chaos, death.
会使你变成一个传奇
This is your legacy.
而我会让你青史留名
I'm your legacy.
要知道有一点我始终不明白
You know what I can't figure out?
你本可以拥有美好的生活
How someone born so rich
可你却选择像畜生一样活着
chooses the poorest path through life.
一个畜生是得不到尊重的
You got no honor.
没有尊重  你也得不到家人的爱
Without honor, you got no family.
失去所有家人
And without family...
将一无所有
...you've got nothing.
因为你我才一无所有
I have nothing because of you.
我的未来  我的家人
My future. My family.
都被你偷走了
You stole that from me.
现在我要一点一点的
And now I'm gonna break yours,
毁掉你的家庭
piece by piece.
你少说废话  有本事站出来
Stop talking and face me.
你喜欢惊喜吗？多姆
Do you like surprises, Dommy?
哈哈  我非常喜欢
I adore them.
游戏还没结束
But the game's not over yet.
很多人还等着我去伤害
There's still so many people to hurt.
我会抓到你的
I'm coming for you.
你戴着手铐可不好抓我
Well, that's gonna be hard to do in handcuffs.
好了  再见  多姆
Okay, bye, Dommy.
不  你先挂断吧
No, you hang up first.
好吧
Okay.
托雷多  别动
Toretto, freeze.
该面对现实了  多姆
Time to face the music, Dom.
警官你这么做就让他得逞了
You're playing right into his hands, cop.
远离交通工具
1组准备集合
封锁周边范围
任务已完成各组成员准备撤退
加油
Okay. Come on.
噢
Oh.
耶
Yeah.
好样的
Great.
好极了
Just great.
狗屎
Shit.
很冷吧
Little chilly?
你的计划还是很差劲
Your plan still sucks.
不过至少你会暖和一点
Maybe, but at least you'll be warm.
“谢谢你,西佩尔,谢谢”
"Thank you, Cipher. Thank you."
这个地方真有货啊
Take a look at this.
这下我们不用愁装备了
This should cover us in the gear department.
我没说会信任你
You are not to be trusted.
我也没把你当做自己人
Hey, you ain't on my Christmas list either.
我要事先说清楚  东西可不是白拿的
Nothing here is for free. Let me be clear on that.
你可千万别忘了找他要收据
Make sure you get a receipt from him, okay?
你不要忘了要收据
I'd love to see that.
鲍伊也不是百无一用
Well, I guess Bowie
我能用他的硬盘驱动器
wasn't entirely worthless. I can use his hard drive
追踪被但丁转走的款项
to complete our trace of Dante.
截止目前他让所有人都进了坑
He's been ten moves ahead of us this whole time.
他一个人是怎么办到的
How does he do it by himself?
哎  这可不太妙
Uh, this isn't good.
我们的钱被转去了全世界各地的账户
Our money, it's been split into accounts all over the world.
看看这些账户都在谁的名下
And look who they're registered to.
他们是雇佣兵杀手团的人  一群真正的人渣
Those are mercenary kill teams. Real scum.
他用我们的钱收买了一支军队
He used our money to buy an army.
这家伙不仅想干掉我们
So this guy doesn't just want us dead.
还想让我们彻底消失
He wants to erase us off the planet.
他想让我们内斗
He's trying to tear us apart.
正是因为这样  我们才需要去集合点
That's exactly why we need to link back up with Dom
和多姆会合
at the rendezvous point.
你来看看这个
You need to see this.
他们不仅会追杀我们
They've been paid to target us
还会追杀帮助过我们的所有人
and anyone who ever helped us until now.
交通工具包在我身上
I'll have transport waiting for you.
那那你要去哪里
And where are you going?
我要送他们进坟墓
I'm gonna dig some graves.
无名氏的得力手下
Mr. Nobody's golden boy,
还没抵抗就乖乖就犯
caught without so much as a fight.
这太无趣了
That's no fun.
这就像大老远跑去珠穆朗玛峰
It's like going all the way to Everest
去选择坐电梯  哈哈哈
and taking the elevator.
你最好系紧安全带
You might want to buckle up.
我知道你为特工局做了不少好事
I know you did some good work for the agency.
我猜你觉得自己能因此被宽大处理
I'm sure you figured that buys you some leniency.
可时代变了  大人
But it's a new day.
话说回来  现在都没人愿意听话了
That's the problem nowadays. Nobody listens.
你该少花点时间研究车子
You should have spent less time with your head under the hood
多花点时间为即将到来的事做准备
and more time preparing for what's coming.
间谍已被人造卫星替代
Spies have been replaced by satellites,
战斗机飞行员被无人机替代  情报局被算法替代
fighter pilots by drones, intelligence by an algorithm.
坐在方向盘后面就能改变世界的日子
The days where one man behind the wheel of a car
已经结束了  多姆
can make a difference are over, Dom.
应该说
Hell, the days of any man
这年头谁坐在方向盘后面都不能改变
behind the wheel of a car are over.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
做好准备  要出事了
Preparing for what's to come.
好吧
Right.
走 走 走
Go. Go. Go.
就在前面交给我
多米尼克  我带你回到了我们初见的地方
Dominic, I brought you back to where we first met.
我为你准备了一个惊喜
And I have a surprise for you.
多姆
Dom!
我现在听你的
I'm listening now.
多米尼克？
Dominic?
多米尼克！
Dominic!
你能别再伤害我的新朋友了吗
Would you stop hurting my new friends?
我来这只是为了伤害你
No. I'm only here to hurt you.
和你说实话吧
I'm not gonna lie to you.
你刚才做的车子特技
That little car stunt you just did?
真是太厉害了
That was pretty awesome.
对不对
Wasn't it?
开的好酷
It was so cool.
你要不停手
But if you don't stop,
我就割她身上的肉  每一个地方
I'm gonna cut her everywhere.
使劲割
Badly.
啊  她在这里呀
There she is.
-哼 -故意晚登场
- Hmm. - Fashionably late.
我输了
You got me.
过去吧
Off you go.
家人
Family.
能从我的车上下来吗
Will you please get off my car?
真是太不尊重人了
That is so disrespectful.
你话可真多
You talk too much.
停下  停下
Stop, stop!
知不知道你的力气有多大
You don't know your own strength.
你混蛋！
You butthole!
等等
Oh, hey.
你喜欢芭蕾吗
Do you like ballet?
我喜欢《天鹅湖》
I adore Swan Lake.
我感觉你像是会喜欢《胡桃夹子》的人哎
I feel like you're more of a-- kind of a Nutcracker guy.
1  2......
And a one, and a two, and...
不要
No!
哈哈哈哈
好戏来了
Wait for it.
哦 不
Oh, no.
她有危险  你会怎么做呢
She's in peril. What will you do?
你知道你的问题是什么吗
You know what your problem is?
家人
Family.
你拯救不了所有人
You can't save 'em all.
5  4
Five. Four.
嗒嗒嗒嗒
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta.
快点哦
Go on.
Two.
你不喜欢芭蕾
You don't like ballet.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
能把天眼给我吗
May I please have the God's Eye?
-别做梦了 -不行吗
- Screw you. - No?
靓女求求你了哦
Pretty please?
找到了哦
Oh, there it is.
到手
Ooh. Gotcha.
交易愉快  车送你了
Good trade. Keep the car.
哎  小多姆
Oh, Dommy!
我跟你说过  我要让你生不如死
I told you, you owe me suffering!
能让你青史留名的不是金钱和权利
Your legacy isn't money or power
也不是组建的家庭和人生的过往
or the family you built or the life you led.
而是你生命的延续
It's the life you made.
父子之情
And a father and his son...
高于一切
is everything.
你在这座桥上杀了我父亲
You killed my father on this bridge.
现在我知道去哪里找你儿子了
And now I know where to find your son.
幸会
Enchanté.
你不会有事的  泰丝  伤口被贯穿了
You're gonna be okay, Tess. It went clear through.
有点疼
Kinda hurts.
你父亲会以你为荣的
Your father would be proud.
是
Yeah.
一定要阻止他
You will stop him.
相信自己
Have faith.
她需要去医院
She needs a hospital.
不会有事的
You're gonna be okay.
把她交给我
I got her.
去救你的儿子
Go save your son.
我的外甥
My nephew.
我不会向你道歉  但我会帮你一个大忙
I'm not gonna say I'm sorry, so let me do you one better.
我们去接你儿子吧
Let's get your son.
(葡萄牙)
这里原来是座老矿山
So, it used to be an old mine,
他们在大山深处炸出了隧道
and they blasted tunnels deep into the mountain.
所以我就
And I just, uh...
重新利用了这个地方
repurposed the place.
你必须相信自己能变废为宝
You just got to keep yourself open to possibilities.
而且当然还要有足够的空闲时间
And, of course,  have a lot of time on your hands.
你说过我们会在这里见到他
You said we'd meet him here.
嘿
Hey.
你了解你爸
You know your dad.
他会安全过来的
He's got to make it safe.
等等就来了
We'll just wait.
我爱你  雅各布叔叔
I love you, Uncle Jakob.
那是什么
What's that?
那个嘛啊  是我一直在忙的一个项目
That? Ah, project I've been working on.
你不会感兴趣的
You wouldn't be interested.
我们正在进入葡萄牙领空
All right, we're entering Portuguese airspace.
雅各布已经到了  多姆有消息吗
Jakob's already there. Any word from Dom?
嘿
Hey.
你怎么这么安静  咋了？
Why are you so quiet? You all right?
我正坐在这思考呢  兄弟
Just been sitting here thinking, man.
怪不得我闻到了一股烧焦味
I knew I smelled something burning in here.
特尔佳  那是我的任务  都在听我指挥
Tej, it was my mission, y'all took my lead,
但我把所有事情搞得一塌糊涂
and I messed this thing up every step of the way.
我感觉
I guess this whole...
我根本就不适合带领你们做事
leadership thing really ain't for me.
你用集装箱把我们运到了伦敦
You took us to London on a container.
你花掉了你的积蓄  那可是你的私房钱
You spent thousands of dollars of your own cash,
绑在你屁股上的钱
strapped to your ass,
现在闻着就像廉价的古龙香水
that now smells like cheap cologne.
此刻你还坐在这里独自担下全责
Now you're sitting here taking sole responsibility
其实我们所有人都有责任
for something that we all wear.
我知道我这话听着挺蠢的
Yeah, I know. It sounds stupid.
不过一点也不蠢
Nah, it don't sound stupid at all.
你猜我听完这话想到了什么
You know what it sounds like to me?
也就领队会说这话
That sounds like a leader.
行了  兄弟快站起来吧  兄弟
Come on, man. Get your ass up, man.
我爱你  哥们
I love you, man.
我也爱你  老弟
I love you, too, bro.
有时候我们必须要道歉
Sometimes we got to say, "I'm sorry."
对不起兄弟我不该打你
I'm sorry for whupping your ass, man,
其实我不是有意的
'cause I didn't really mean to do that.
整件事情
The whole thing, it would've been a whole dif... -
-你怎么了 -没事吧
- You okay? - What's wrong?
你的蠢话害我过敏了
I'm just allergic to your bullshit.
去你的  哈哈哈
Come on.
哎  敲慢点  小心敲坏了
Hey, go easy there. You're gonna break that thing.
你还好吧
You all right?
天眼刚刚派了几十个雇佣兵追杀
God's Eye was just used to send
多姆的儿子
dozens of mercenaries after Dom's son.
我创造的东西正在毁掉我爱的一切
Something I created hurting the people we love.
本想要它来帮忙的
It was meant to help.
它的危害远大于但丁
This is bigger than just Dante.
它的能量远大于我们
This is bigger than just us.
我们必须马上阻止这个怪物
We have to stop this monster now.
我们得走了
We got to go.
抓紧了
Hold on!
我看到肌肉叔叔和那个孩子了
I got eyes on Uncle Muscle and the kid.
好了  各位重申一下计划
All right, everybody, remember the plan.
先抓再绑  谢谢
Contain and kidnap. Thank you.
不行
No.
不准用枪
No guns.
这小子必须活着
I need this little shit alive.
起码现在不能死
At least for a while.
-准备好了吗 -好了
- You ready? - Ready.
我勒个大…草
Holy sh...
没事  没事  说脏活吧
Oh, no, you're good. You're good.
都可以说唱歌词  磕到脚趾  还有开加侬炮车的时候
Okay, uh, song lyrics, stubbed toes and cannon cars.
好的
Yeah.
开始吧
Here we go!
卡住了  卡住了
It's stuck. It's stuck.
他们人手众多  多姆
They got an army down there, Dom.
你的队员离那不远
Your team's not far out.
-准备降落了 -我不能在这里降落
- Bring us down. - I can't put her down here.
西边7千米处有个机场
There's an airfield seven klicks west.
好  我们在那里汇合  打开后舱门
Okay, we'll meet you there. Now open the back.
多姆  真的没地方可以降落
Dom, there's really nowhere to land.
谁说让你降落
Who said anything about landing?
瞧
Look.
我这就过去找你  儿子
I'm coming for you, son.
搞什么
What the...
-爸爸 -嘿  儿子
- Dad! - Hey, son.
很高兴见到你  大哥
Good to see you, big bro.
很高兴见到你们  跟着我到飞机那边去
Good to see you guys. Follow me to that plane.
我们跟着你
We're right behind you.
这次别想跑
I got you now.
爱慕斯  我们在路上了
Aimes, we're on our way.
多姆  我会在西边5千米处降落
Dom, I'll be touching down five klicks west.
但他们还在你后面
But they're still on your tail.
卡住了
It's jammed.
小布  你要做什么
B, what are you doing?
小心点
Careful.
好好好
Okay, okay, okay.
有没有搞错
Shut the front door.
小布
Little B.
雅格布叔叔
Uncle Jakob!
我修好了
I fixed it!
小布
B!
拜拜喽
Toodle-oo.
-救命 -嗒嗒嗒嗒  闭嘴
- Help! - Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta. Shut up.
该死
Damn it.
一起来点刺激的
You party? I party.
喔
Whoa.
多姆  我跟丢了 但丁抓走了小布
Dom, I lost him. Dante has Little B.
嘿  多米尼克  欢迎来到决战环节
Hey, Dominic. Welcome to the big showdown.
比赛接近尾声了  瞧瞧我的副驾驶
It's the last lap. Check out my copilot.
-爸爸 -谁能料到会是这样
- Dad! - Who could've seen this coming?
除了我之外
I mean, you know, except for me.
该死  我的燃油管好像坏了
Shit. Looks like my fuel line's been shot.
-我追不上他  多姆 -雅各布  你跟着我
- I can't get to him, Dom. - Jakob, stay with me.
我要出局了
I'm out of this race.
只能靠你了
It has to be you.
嗨  多姆  为你准备了个小惊喜
Hey, Dom! Got a little surprise for you.
你养了个好儿子  多姆
You raised a hell of a son, Dom.
我该从你的阴影里走出来了
Time for me to step out from under your shadow.
谢谢你点亮了我的人生
Thanks for showing me the light.
雅各布？
Jakob?
我会为你铲除障碍
I'm gonna go clear the way.
去夺回你儿子
Go get your son.
雅各布  不要！
Jakob, don't!
不要
Don't!
雅各布叔叔
Uncle Jakob!
看来你的壮汉叔叔  没法参加下次的烧烤派对了  哈哈哈
Looks like Uncle Muscle won't be coming to the next barbecue.
嗯
Oh.
我是说他死的真光荣
I mean, it's very honorable.
距离5公里  驶入辅路
Three miles away. Take the service road.
你能一路开到机场
It'll lead you right to the airfield.
怎么在街头赛打败你爸爸
You know how to beat your dad in a street race?
把他带离街头
Take away the streets.
爸爸！
Dad!
太棒了
Amazing.
没事的  没事的
We got it. We got it.
该我了
My turn.
厉害  你爸真厉害
He's good. Your dad's good.
多姆  还有1.6公里
Dom, you got one mile left.
儿子  我说过我是信守承诺的人
Son, I never break a promise.
一起来上完那趟驾驶课
Now, let's finish that driving lesson.
感受车
Feel the car,
找准线
find your line
飞速疾驰
and fly.
跳
Now!
不
No.
现在走辅路
Take the service road now.
-我已经降落了 -我们现在就去找你
- I'm wheels down. - We're headed to you now.
你的人已经在路上了
Your team is on their way.
我们在机场汇合
I'll meet you at the airfield.
-你还好吗 -我没事了  爸
- You okay? - I'm good, Dad.
我为你骄傲  儿子
I'm real proud of you, son.
哦  小多姆
Oh, Dommy boy.
真高兴再次见到你
It's so good to see you again.
你刚才是用直升飞机打我了吗
Did you hit me with a helicopter back there?
哼  哈哈哈
Hmm.
好疼啊  你这个大块头  我懂
Ow, you big brute. I mean, I get it.
你在儿子面前炫技呢
You're showing off in front of your son.
但说真的  你以为我那么容易
But honestly, did you really think
就会被干掉吗
it was going to be that easy?
和我计划的一样  你到达了指定地点
You're exactly where I wanted you to be.
没错
Yes.
等着吧
Wait for it.
给你准备的惊喜
I got a surprise for you.
骑士们到了  交给我们吧  多姆
The cavalry's here. We got you, Dom.
罗曼  快离开  这是圈套
Roman, get out of here. It's a trap.
他们打过来了
Incoming!
太棒了
Yes!
这就是家人太多的问题所在
See, that's the problem with having a big family.
没法保护所有人
Can't protect 'em all.
哦  多米尼克  那是你的新朋友吗
Oh, Dominic, is that your new friend?
你太有预见性了
You are so predictable.
你以为所有人都会成为你的朋友吗
You think everyone's gonna end up on your side?
问题是爱姆斯首先是我的家人
Problem is Aimes was mine first.
行动已经开始了
Now the work begins.
那么从今天起
And in there,
我们会将家族带上真正的权力之路
today we'll put our family on a path to real power.
好了  我们开始吧
Let's get started.
看起来我们的合作关系
Well, looks like our partnership's
刚开始就很精彩
off to a fantastic start.
知道吗  多姆  想成为真圣人
You know, Dominic, to become a real saint,
你必须能创造奇迹
you have to perform miracles.
或者殉道而死
Or die a martyr.
你要怎么选择呢
So what's it gonna be?
(远程操控)
我夺走了你的钱  你的自由
I took your money, I took your freedom,
我还要夺走你的家人
and I'm gonna take your family.
现在你小命不保
And you're gonna die
你的儿子也要一起死了
knowing that you couldn't save your son.
爸爸
Dad.
相信自己
I have faith.
你犯了个错误
You made one mistake.
你没夺走我的车
You never took my car.
折磨已经结束了  多姆
The suffering is over, Dom.
是时候杀掉你了
It's time for you to die.
不可能
No way.
还认为我的计划差劲吗
Still think my plan sucks?
(未知来电)
你好呀  伙计
Howdy, partner.
你喜欢惊喜吗？
Do you like surprises?
你做了一些令人发指的事情  警长
You've done some dastardly, dirty deeds, Sheriff.
你带走了我生命中最珍贵的东西
You took the most important thing in my life from me.
多姆  在开车
Dom drove the car.
-但是你… -救救我
- But you... -  Help me.
……你扣动了扳机
...you pulled the trigger.
现在  我要开始折磨你了
And now I'm gonna make you suffer.
魔鬼要来找你了……
The devil is coming for you...
警长先生
lawman.
我很好找的  混蛋
Well, I ain't hard to find, you sumbitch.